Finding Aid for Medical School (University of Michigan) records, 1850-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Records 1915-1996
  - Administrative Series 1950-1998
    - 1983-1998
      - Medical Scientist Training Program (MSTP)
        - General 1991-1996, 3 folders (Box 302)
        - Director Search 1991 (Box 308)
        - MSTP Site Visit 1994 (Box 302)
      - Medical Service Plan (MSP) (Box 303)
        - General 1991-1996 (Box 303)
        - Director-Position Description and Organizational Chart 1987 (Box 303)
        - Director Search 1988-1989 (Box 308)
        - MSP Exchange of Services 1988-1990 (Box 303)
      - Medical Services Organization 1995-1996 (Box 303)
      - Medicare/Medicaid 1991, 1996, 2 folders (Box 303)
      - Medstart Conference 1993 (Box 303)
      - Michigan Medical Schools-Council of Deans 1987, 1990-1993, 3 folders (Box 303)
      - Minority Affairs -- Associate Dean for Minority Affairs Director Search 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 308)
      - Minority Student Recruitment 1993 (Box 303)
      - Morgan Stanley 1995-1996 (Box 303)
      - Networking 1990 (Box 303)
      - Networking 1996 (Box 303)
        (Subcommittee of Faculty Group Practice Board of Directors and Clinical Delivery System Executive Committee)
      - Neuroscience 1990-1992, 1993, 2 folders (Box 303)
      - Nuclear Medicine 1996 (Box 303)
      - Organogenesis 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 303)
      - Outside Checking Accounts 1989-1990 (Box 303)
      - Parking Fund Agreement 1992 (Box 303)
      - Pediatrics' 75th Anniversary Committee 1996 (Box 303)
      - Personnel
        - General 1990, 1993, 2 folders (Box 304)
        - Personnel 1990 (Box 308)
      - Pharmacia/Upjohn 1996 (Box 304)
      - Planning and Marketing, Office of 1990, 1992, 2 folders (Box 304)
      - Post-Baccalaureate Program 1995 (Box 308)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July. 1 2071 ]
      - Practice Plan Financial Update 1996 (Box 304)
      - Primary Care Consultants 1993-1994 (Box 304)
      - Prison 1989-1992 (Box 304)
      - Program in Society and Medicine 1992-1994 (Box 304)
      - Quality Management Program (Box 304)
      - Recruitment, Retention, and Career Development Task Force 1990-1991 (Box 304)
      - Regents
        - Regents 1990-1992, 1995-1997, 5 folders (Box 304)
        - Regents' Briefings
          - McFee Briefing March 1991 (Box 304)
          - Briefing 1995 (Box 304)
          - Regents Deitch and Horning June 1996 (Box 304)
      - Research
        - Research 1989-1993, 4 folders (Box 304)
        - Research 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 305)
        - Research Advisory Committee 1992 (Box 305)
        - Assistant Dean for Research 1990-1991 (Box 308)
        - Associate Dean for Research (Irwin Goldstein) 1985-1989 (Box 305)
        - Biomedical Research Support Grant 1990 (Box 305)
        - Conduct of Research 1986-1991 (Box 305)
        - Conflict of Interest 1989-1993 (Box 305)
        - Fixed-Price Contracts 1988-1990 (Box 305)
        - Indirect Costs 1990-1992, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 305)
        - Reproductive Sciences Program 1990 (Box 305)
        - Research Space 1989-1990, 1992, 2 folders (Box 305)
      - Salary Task Force 1996 (Box 305)
      - Sandoz Research Institute 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 305)
      - School of Public Health 1996 (Box 305)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) 1990-1992, 1995, 2 folders (Box 305)
      - Senior Administrative Officer (Schrodel) 1989-1996 (Box 308)
      - Senior Scientist 1993-1994 (Box 305)
      - Shiga University Agreement 1990-1991 (Folder UBImu C46)
      - Simpson Memorial Institute 1995, 1998 (Box 305)
      - SmithKline Beecham 1997-1998 (Box 305)
      - South Central Michigan Health Alliance 1998 (Box 305)
      - Staff Salary 1993 (Box 305)
      - Strategic Options 1996 (Box 305)
      - Strategic Plans 1990-1992 (Box 305)
      - Student Programs (formerly Academic Programs)
        - Admissions 1990-1996, 5 folders (Box XXX)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July. 1 2071 removed to box XXX]
        - Associate Dean for Academic/Student Programs (Thomas Shope) 1991-1993 (Box 309)
        - Associate Dean for Student Programs (Marshall Shlafer)--Meetings with Bole 1992-1993 (Box 309)
        - Associate Dean for Student Programs Search 1997 (Box 309)
        - Student Files 1991-1995 (Box 309)
        - Student Problems 1995-1997 (Box 309)
        - Student Problems--Individual Students, 15 folders (Box 309)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July. 1 2072 ]
        - Student Programs 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 309)
      - Substance Abuse Policy 1989-1991 (Box 305)
      - Target of Opportunity Program 1990-1990 (Box 306)
      - Taubman Improvement Task Force 1996 (Box 306)
      - Teaching Physician Task Force 1996 (Box 306)
      - Teaching Portfolio 1989-1996, 2 folders (Box 306)
      - Technology Development 1992-1994 (Box 306)
      - Technology Development and Transfer Activities 1995-1997, 2 folders (Box 306)
      - Telemedicine 1997 (Box 306)
      - Town Hall Slide Presentations 1994 (Box 306)
      - Tuition 1996-1997 (Box 306)
      - U.S. News 1991-1996 (Box 306)
      - University of Michigan Executive Offices
        - President's Office
          - Duderstadt 1988-1993 (Box 306)
          - President Duderstadt Meeting May 1993 (Box 306)
        - Provost's Office
          - General Correspondence 1989-1995, 5 folders (Box 306)
          - Provost's Office Evaluations 1993 (Box 309)
          - Individual Provosts
            - Cantor (Nancy) 1997 (Box 306)
            - Duderstadt (James J.) 1986-1988 (Box 306)
            - Duderstadt Retreat Follow-Up 1987-1988 (Box 306)
            - Meeting with Bernie Machen 8/29/1995 (Box 307)
            - Machen (J. Bernard) 1997 (Box 307)
            - Vest (Charles) Letter February 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 307)
            - Whitaker (Gil) Meetings 1990-1994, 7 folders (Box 307)
        - Vice Presidents' Offices
          - Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (Ferris Womack) 1991-1993 (Box 307)
          - Meeting with Drs. Womack, Zuidema, Bole June 1991 (Box 307)
          - Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer 1996 (Box 307)
          - Vice President for Research 1990-1993, 1996, 2 folders (Box 307)
          - Vice Provost for Information Technology (Douglas VanHouweling) 1993 (Box 307)
          - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs (George Zuidema) 1989-1993, 4 folders (Box 307)
          - Vice Provost for Minority Affairs 1991 (Box 307)
      - Upjohn Center 1990-1991 (with earlier background material, 1966-1983) (Box 307)
      - Value Centered Management (VCM) 1995-1996 (Box 307)
      - VanAndel Institute 1996-1997 (Box 307)
      - Victor Vaughan Memorial 1995 (Box 307)
      - Visiting Committee 1993, 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box 307)
      - Warner Lambert-Parke Davis 1990-1993, 3 folders (Box 307)
      - Warner Lambert-Parke Davis--Zuiderweg Recruitment (1990-1991) (Box 307)
      - Whitaker Foundation Grant File 1992-1995 (Box 307)
      - Wilpon Pathogenesis Corporation 1992 (Box 307)
  - Miscellaneous Files 1968-1975, 1980-1996
    The series of Miscellaneous Files (3.5 linear feet, 1968-1975, 1980-1996) includes records from the tenures of interim dean Peter Ward (1982-1985), dean Joseph Johnson III (1985-1990), dean Giles Bole (1990-1996) and interim dean A. Lorris Betz (1996-1998), as well as files created during earlier deanships that were retained by Ward when he became interim dean. There are three major components of this series: records of a Medical School task force headed by A. Lorris Betz charged to improve communications in the school, records relating to the Medical School's efforts to assess its climate for diversity, and records pertaining to the process the Medical School undergoes every several years to receive re-accreditation by the American Association of Medical Colleges' Liaison Committee on Medical Education. This last topic is also covered in the Administrative series of subject files.
    - 1968-1975 1980-1996
      - Communications Task Force
        - Planning 1994-1995 (Box 311)
        - Focus Groups April-June, 1995 (Box 311)
        - Focus Group Minutes: (Box 311)
        - Clinical Faculty and Clinical Trainees April 1995 (Box 311)
        - Scientific Faculty and Scientific Trainees April 1995 (Box 311)
        - Staff and Medical Administration Staff April 1995 (Box 311)
      - Diversity Committee Background Materials 1992-1993 (Box 311)
      - Diversity Committee 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 311)
      - Cultural Diversity Assessment
        - Preliminary Materials 1994-1995 (Box 311)
        - Proposal 1994-1995 (Box 311)
        - Steering Committee 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 311)
        - Interviews March-May 1995 (Box 312)
        - Focus Groups March-May 1995 (Box 312)
        - Survey, May-October 1995 (Box 312)
        - Report and Requests February-May 1996 (Box 312)
        - Newspaper Articles March-April, 1996 (Box 312)
      - Liaison Committee for Medical Education (LCME)
        - Pre-1980 Accreditation Materials (1968-1975) (Box 312)
        - 1982 LCME Accreditation
          - Institutional Self-Study March 1982 (Box 312)
          - Medical Education Data Base, Parts I-XV 1982 (Box 312)
          - Medical Education Data Base, Part XVII--Clinical Science Departments 1982 (Box 312)
          - Self-Study Blank Questionnaires April 1982 (Box 312)
          - Correspondence and Supporting Information 1981-1982 (Box 313)
          - Report of the Ad-Hoc Survey Team May 1982 (Box 313)
        - LCME Progress reports and Correspondence 1982-1984 (Box 313)
        - LCME Fellowship 1987-1989 (Box 313)
        - 1990 LCME Accreditation
          - Self-Study Planning 1988-1989 (Box 313)
          - Governance and Administration Subcommittee April-June, 1989 (Box 313)
          - Orientation Meeting at AMA Meeting June 17, 1989 (Box 313)
          - Site Visit Planning 1988-1990 (Box 313)
          - Institutional Self-Study Report 1990, 1 volumes (Box 313)
          - Medical Education Data Base Sections I-X 1990, 2 volumes (Box 313)
          - Medical Education Data Base Section XI-A--Basic Science Departments 1990, 1 volumes (Box 313)
          - Medical Education Data Base Section XI-B--Clinical Science Departments 1990, 1 volumes (Box 314)
      - Miscellaneous Reports 1991, 1996 (Box 314)
  - Allen Lichter, Dean 1998-2006
    In 2008 and 2010, the Bentley Library received small accessions of digital materials (from the Office of the Provost and the Office of the Medical School Dean, respectively) related to the Medical School. These materials comprise a new series, Allen Lichter, Dean 1998-2006, within the Dean's Records subgroup. Content includes a "State of the School" address delivered by Dean Allen S. Lichter at Dow Auditorium in the Towsley Center on May 25, 2004 (with presentation slides and video footage of the event) and email correspondence from 1999-2006. This correspondence deals with faculty recruiting, professional medical boards, event logistics, and communication with donors, Medical School faculty, and administration.
    - Email Correspondence 1998-2006
      (BHL deposit ID 87253_0002)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2028 ]
    - State of the School Address 2004
      (BHL deposit ID 87253_0001)
- Subordinate Administrative Officers 1929-1998
  The Subordinate Administrative Officers subgroup, 1929-1998, is divided into fifteen series, one for each subordinate administrator whose papers are located within the subgroup. Most often these individuals held the rank of associate dean. The subgroup is incomplete in that all senior administrators within the school are not represented. It is also incomplete in that the records of the named administrators are not whole. Generally, the files located in this subgroup are of residual, rather than essential, documents. Unless otherwise noted, each series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Alexander Barry, Associate Dean 1961-1969
    Associate Dean Alexander Barry's Series (1961-1969) consists largely of construction records for projects built during his years of service. A great deal of the correspondence is with J. A. Diana, who seems to have been responsible for day-to-day oversight of the construction projects.
    - Admissions Material 1961-1968 (Box 83)
    - Ambulatory Care Unit 1963 (Box 83)
    - Animal Care Committee 1963-1965 (Box 83)
    - Animal Research Facility
      - Project 189
        - General 1961-1965 (Box 83)
        - Specifications (Box 84)
      - Project 261 1960-1969 (Box 84)
    - Audio-Visual Education Facilities 1963-1968 (Box 84)
    - Bio-Engineering 1962-1966 (Box 84)
    - Buhl Research Center for Human Genetics 1963-1967 (Box 84)
    - Communication Sciences 1963 (Box 84)
    - Council on the Basic Sciences 1963-1964 (Box 84)
    - Dental Research Unit 1965-1967 (Box 84)
    - Gerber Children's Research Laboratory (Mott A) 1967 (Box 84)
    - Health Sciences Information Center 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Kresge Medical Research Building Construction 1961-1965
      - General (Box 84)
      - Grant Proposal (Box 84)
      - Building Specifications, 2 volumes (Box 85)
    - Medical Center
      - Long Range Program Projections 1965-1966 (Box 85)
      - Open Space Study 1967 (Box 85)
      - Planning Committee 1961-1966 (Box 85)
      - Planning Report 1961 (Box 85)
    - Medical Library 1962-1964 (Box 85)
    - Medical Records 1963 (Box 85)
    - Medical Science II Construction
      - General, 2 folders (Box 85)
      - Department Program Content 1962 (Box 85)
      - Memorandum of Record 1951-1963 prepared 1963 (Box 85)
      - Minutes 1962-1968, 2 folders (Box 85)
      - Program Statement 1963 (Box 85)
      - Space Utilization
        - Specifications (Box 86)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 86)
    - C. S. Mott Hospital
      - General (Box 86)
      - Minutes 1964-1968 (Box 86)
      - Specifications (Box 86)
      - Mott A 1964 (Box 86)
    - Parkview Medical Center 1967 (Box 86)
    - Planning Conference, North Campus 1965 (Box 86)
    - Rackham Arthritis Research Unit Annual Report 1963-1964 (Box 86)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute Renovation 1962-1967 (Box 86)
    - University Hospital
      - Expansion Plans 1967 (Box 86)
      - Renovation 1965-1965 (Box 86)
    - Veterans Hospital, Anesthesia Agreement 1965 (Box 86)
  - George R. DeMuth, Associate Dean 1964-1977
    The papers of Associate Dean George R. DeMuth date from 1964 to 1977. DeMuth was primarily responsible for academic affairs within the school. His series contains an extensive group of committee records.
    - American Association of Medical Colleges Curriculum Conference 1968
      - General, 2 folders (Box 86)
      - UM Questionnaire (Box 86)
    - Administrative Fellowships 1974 (Box 87)
    - Allied Health: Report of the Subcommittee on the University Policies in Teaching and Organization of the Health Related Professions 1970 (Box 87)
    - Appeals Procedure for Teaching Staff 1970-1972 (Box 87)
    - Authorization for Program in Cellular and Molecular Biology 1971-1973 (Box 87)
    - Committees
      - Academic Programs
        - Minutes 1969-1970 (Box 87)
        - Miscellaneous 1964-1969, 3 folders (Box 87)
      - Ad Hoc Committee for Curriculum Appraisal
        - Final Report and Minutes 1968-1970 (Box 87)
        - Questionnaires (Box 87)
        - Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 87)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Computer Activities 1969-1971 (Box 87)
      - Community Medicine, Committee on Program in
        - Carpenter, Robert 1971-1972 (Box 88)
        - Clinical Scholarship Program Proposal 1973 (Box 88)
        - Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 88)
        - Nurse Practitioner/Physician Assistant Program Proposal 1972 (Box 88)
      - Curricular Appraisal 1969 (Box 88)
      - Liaison Committee on Medical Education (AMA) Questionnaire 1969-1973 (Box 88)
      - Michigan Medical Schools Liaison Committee
        - Appropriations 1971-1976, 6 folders (Box 88)
        - Cost Allocations 1974-1977, 5 folders (Box 88)
        - Meetings 1973
          - March 7 (Box 88)
          - May 30 (Box 88)
          - June 29 (Box 88)
          - August 8 (Box 89)
          - September 7 (Box 89)
          - October 31, 1973-May 1974 (Box 89)
        - Reports 1973 (Box 89)
      - Optometry 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Optometry Education 1973-1974 (Box 89)
    - Correspondence 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Course Credit Hour Study 1970 (Box 89)
    - Course Offerings of Medical School 1969-1973, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Faculty Conference on Curriculum 1967-1969, 3 folders (Box 89)
    - Grant Proposal to Improve Quality of Medical Education 1968-1970 (Box 89)
    - Interns and Residents Association 1971-1973 (Box 89)
    - Joint MD-Ph.D. Program 1963-1972 (Box 89)
    - Medical Center Administrative Staff Meetings 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Medical Science Training Program 1970-1972 (Box 89)
    - Memos 1968-1976, 5 folders (Box 90)
    - Michigan State Legislature, Reports to 1971-1974, 2 folders (Box 90)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners 1967-1968 (Box 90)
    - Neural and Behavioral Science 1973 (Box 90)
    - Pediatrics
      - Correspondence 1971-1974 (Box 90)
      - Syllabus 1974 (Box 90)
    - Physician's Assistant 1970-1971 (Box 90)
    - Professional and Administrative Staff Study 1972-1976 (Box 90)
    - Scholarships and Loans 1971 (Box 90)
    - Staff Questionnaire 1969 (Box 90)
    - Western Michigan Comprehensive Health Services Project (Lake County Project) 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Robert A. Green, Associate Dean 1961-1977
    Associate Dean Robert A. Green's Series (1961-1977) includes extensive information about affirmative action programs within the school (1962-1977), joint staff meeting minutes (1976-1977) and material regarding the core (affiliated) hospitals (1971-1976).
    - Administrative Structure of the Dean's Office 1971-1975 (Box 90)
    - Admissions Materials 1961-1968 (Box 90)
    - Affirmative Action
      - Medical School Compliance Reports
        - 1962-1963 (Box 90)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 90)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 90)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 90)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 90)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 90)
        - 1968-1969
          - General Report (Box 90)
          - Department Reports (Box 90)
        - 1970-1971
          - General Report (Box 90)
          - Background (Box 90)
          - Department Reports (Box 91)
          - Women (Box 91)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 91)
        - 1972-1973
          - Department Reports (Box 91)
          - Availability Assessments of Staff (Box 91)
          - Students (Box 91)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 91)
    - Allied Health Education 1973-1975 (Box 91)
    - Alpha Omega Alpha Honorary Society 1974 (Box 91)
    - Beaumont Hospital 1974 (Box 91)
    - Budget Projections 1975 (Box 91)
    - By-laws
      - Medical Staff
        - 1973 (Box 91)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 91)
      - Regents (Box 91)
    - Clinical Resources 1974-1975 (Box 91)
    - Clinical Sequence Questionnaire 1975-1976 (Box 91)
    - Committees
      - Academic Affairs
        - Reorganization 1975 (Box 91)
        - Promotions 1973-1977 (Box 91)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation 1974 (Box 91)
      - Dean's Mini-staff Meetings
        - October, 1975 (Box 91)
        - November-December, 1975 (Box 91)
        - 1976 (Box 92)
      - Dean's Staff
        - General 1970-1975 (Box 92)
        - Meetings 1974-1977, 4 folders (Box 92)
        - Decision Making Structure 1976 (Box 92)
      - Department of Defense Advisory Council 1972 (Box 92)
      - Executive Committee
        - General
          - 1974-1975 (Box 92)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 92)
        - Retreat 1976 (Box 92)
      - Governance Clarification Committee
        - Report 1975 (Box 92)
        - Minutes and Memoranda 1975-1975 (Box 92)
        - Background 1973-1974 (Box 92)
      - Joint Staff Meetings
        - 1976
          - March-April (Box 92)
          - May (Box 92)
          - June (Box 93)
          - July (Box 93)
          - August (Box 93)
          - September-December (Box 93)
        - 1977
          - January-June (Box 93)
          - July-November (Box 93)
      - Junior Medical Advisory Staff Meetings 1968 (Box 93)
      - Medical Center Administrative Group 1973-1974 (Box 93)
      - Medical Center Administrative Staff
        - 1970-1972 (Box 93)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 93)
      - Medical Center Board in Control 1973-1974
        - Bylaws (Box 93)
        - General (Box 93)
      - Medical Center Mini-Group (core administrators) 1973-1974 (Box 93)
      - Medical Center Review Committee 1972-1974 (Box 94)
      - Replacement Hospital Project, Task Force
        - Minutes 1972, 1974, 2 folders (Box 94)
        - Functional Program Document January 25, 1974 (Box 94)
      - Review and Search Committees 1972-1976, 2 folders (Box 94)
      - Student Governance, Commission to Study 1975 (Box 94)
    - Connors, Edward J., Resignation 1974 (Box 94)
    - Core Hospitals
      - Basic Data 1971-1976 (Box 94)
      - Budgets 1973-1974 (Box 94)
      - Henry Ford Hospital (Box 94)
      - Highland Park General Hospital 1973 (Box 94)
      - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital 1975 (Box 94)
      - Veterans Administration Hospital 1967-1976 (Box 94)
      - Wayne County General Hospital 1975-1976 (Box 94)
    - Cost Model of Education 1975 (Box 94)
    - Curriculum 1973-1975 (Box 94)
    - Dentistry, School of 1975 (Box 94)
    - Diabetes Center Proposal 1976 (Box 94)
    - Effort Analysis 1974-1975 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Retreats 1966-1976 (Box 94)
    - Furstenberg Student Center (Box 95)
      - Fund Raising 1972 (Box 95)
      - General 1973-1974 (Box 95)
    - Grade Recording System 1974 (Box 95)
    - Graduate Medical Education 1973-1975 (Box 95)
    - Health Service Agencies 1976 (Box 95)
    - Health Service Research Group 1971-1974 (Box 95)
    - House Officers Association 1973-1976 (Box 95)
    - Interdepartmental Programs, Neural and Behavioral Science 1975 (Box 95)
    - Interdisciplinary Programs 1974-1977 (Box 95)
    - Intern Resident Association 1970-1974, 4 folders (Box 95)
    - Intern Resident Data 1972-1974 (Box 95)
    - Internal Department Review 1947-1966 (Box 95)
    - Medical Center Alumni Society
      - General 1974 (Box 95)
      - Visiting Committee 1976 (Box 95)
    - Medical Center Organization 1974 (Box 95)
    - Medical Center Planning Office 1970-1975 (Box 95)
    - Medical Center Visiting Committee Participant List 1976 (Box 95)
    - Medical School Review 1974-1975 (Box 95)
    - Michigan Association for Graduate and Postgraduate Medical Education 1970-1974 (Box 95)
    - Primary Care/Community Medicine 1974-1975 (Box 96)
    - Professional Fees (Medical Service Plan) 1970-1975, 4 folders (Box 96)
    - Program in Community Medicine, Report to the Dean June 1969 (Box 96)
    - Resource Allocation Priorities Questionnaire 1977 (Box 96)
    - Special Studies Program 1960-1968, 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Turner Geriatric Health Center Planning 1973-1977 (Box 96)
    - University Hospital
      - Director Search 1974 (Box 96)
      - Mission and Role Statement 1974-1977 (Box 96)
  - Thomas J. Herrmann, Associate Dean 1960-1977